We're on the golf course!
Yay!
Oh!
May I call you Lena?
Sure.
You broke your driver once.
Heh.
Oh!
I'm Erena Mori, Sakurazaka 46.
I'm Reina Odakura.
Good evening.
As you can probably tell by looking at us right now.
We're here at the golf course.
Yay!
We came here today to practice our golf game.
Reina-chan...
As you all know, I used to play golf.
A little bit when I was in high school.
Just a little.
I'm sure she's good at it.
I saw your video of Moriya-san.
You saw it?
He was so good!
I'm lying.
It can't be!
I'm a beginner. I've only just started playing.
I've only been able to practice a few times.
but I'd like to have fun practicing with you today.
I'm sure we'll have fun practicing together today!
I'm sure we'll have a lot of fun! I think so.
I will do my best from now on.
I'll do my best.
So let's get started... practice.
Okay, let's start.
Okay, we're going to practice a little bit.
Which one do you want to start with?
I'm going to start with you, Moriya.
No, no, Reina-chan first.
Me... not at all...
I'm not very good at this.
Let's start with someone who's done it before.
First...
Reina-chan.
Reina!
What's that for?
What's that?
What number?
Oh, this is a 7 iron.
A 7-iron.
Yes, sir.
Seven.
That's good, that's great, it's going to the right.
I heard that's pretty rare.
I should've just gone ahead like a normal person.
I'm so nervous now... on the contrary...
What's your number, Moriya?
I'll be on 9.
Don't think too hard. It's hard. I'm scared.
I'm scared. Yes, sir.
Oh, my God! It flew so high!
You're so cute when you hit it.
Isn't she cute? Reina was cuter.
Wow!
Nice sound!
It's good!
It sure sounded good.
She's cute!
I like the direction you're going in.
White fluffy clothes.
Fluffy.
So cute.
White, white on top.
And the ponytail.
They're the same.
How old is the real one?
Ninety-nine.
That's really nice.
Oh, my God! That's good, that's good, that's good!
How many? 100!
A hundred! That's great!
Moriya's all white. He's so cute.
Wow! How do you make it fly?
When I was in high school, I was told to go with the rhythm.
Rhythm.
One, two, three... I see.
Rhythm. That's for sure.
Oh!
Wow! Wow!
It was flying straight and true.
Can I call you Lena?
Sure!
Here.
I'm glad.
I wanted to call you that.
Call me Lena.
I'm so glad.
Thank you.
I called you Lena.
How's your golf game today?
Heh.
It's been almost a month since I've seen you.
Oh, we did, didn't we?
What was that thing you were doing?
You were flying.
Yeah, we did the light ones.
I remember.
Ever since then, almost since then.
I'm kind of nervous about it.
I'm a beginner. I'm a beginner.
I'm so excited every time I hit it.
I'm so bad at it.
I'm not very good at it.
Rena, you were great.
How did you get into golf?
Golf?
Family? Family?
All of my family members play golf.
I started playing golf in high school because I thought it looked like fun when I saw them playing together on vacation.
I'm the same way... my family all played golf and it looked like a lot of fun.
They told me to play golf a lot, but I never got interested in it.
But it wasn't until recently that I decided I wanted to try it for the first time, so I gave it a shot.
It's really good.
It's good?
I want to get better at it.
How's it going? How are you today, Moriya?
Not at all, not at all.
I don't know, not at all.
I want to be able to hit like a bat out of hell, and fast.
I'm not doing well at all
I'll change clubs and hit a little more
Moriya, you're on 9, Rena.
Rena's on 9.
Oh, it's no good! It was flying so straight!
You're following me, Rayna.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, I'll try the driver.
Have a good day.
Oh!
Oh! That looks like it's gonna fly great.
Aah! It went really far to the right!
Oh my gosh, it's flying!
It's getting scary high!
Oh, that feels good.
I was like, "How does that feel?
Thank you Thank you.
Then, why don't you try to be a driver?
A little bit of a screwdriver, that's for sure.
I'll give it a try.
I broke my screwdriver once.
It made a noise like "clunk, clunk, clunk.
Inside?
I broke it by hitting it in a weird place.
I'm a little scared because I broke it once.
But I'll give it a try.
Put your feet together like this.
Get ready.
And pull.
Hold it like that.
Like this.
I see.
That's easy to understand.
If you make him do it, he'll raise the bread right off the floor. It's really not that great.
To the left.
That sounded so good!
That feels good.
It's just a nice sound.
You're not a very good driver yet, are you?
Is that a blue flag?
Is it at the far end?
That's where we're aiming for.
It's all in the mind, that's for sure.
Well, that could change.
Oh, that's nice.
Sounds good, Yuuchan. Sounds good, Yuuchan.
It's about 123.
Isn't today the best day?
Yes, the best today.
That's great.
Oh, wow!
It flew! It flew!
I don't think he's convinced.
I knew you didn't teach me how to drive.
I'm going to give up on the driver.
I'm going to go back to my original driver.
Go, go, go, go!
What did I do today? I didn't look, but I think this is the best I've seen it today. 95.
Ninety-five? Of all the times today. Okay, I'm going to try what you taught me.
I'm going to try lowering my right shoulder a little bit. I wonder if I can get in.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow! Teacher! Thank you.
It flew a little. It flew really well.
Straight up, so serious, with a straight face
I was too serious... I can see it now...
It's your turn, Rena. I'll do my best. I'll do number 7.
Straight ahead. You went pretty far into the blue.
Looking good.
Nice!
I love it.
That sounded good.
Okay, three balls at a time.
I'm nervous.
Shall we do it?
What number do you use? What number do you use?
Certainly, number 9.
Number nine.
Yes, I'll use Kitching.
Yes, sir.
Let's do our best.
Good luck.
It's so far to the right.
Yes, sir.
That looks good. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Here comes the last one.
Not even close.
The club is pitching.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Rust.
Well, we're in the right place.
So... well... the showdown... but Raina was doing really well... at 60.
I think she was doing it... really well... and she even said she was in the second grade.
I think it's difficult, but I want to work harder so that I can get it to where I want it to go.
I'd like to work harder so that I can fly where I'm aiming for.
Mr. Penner and Ms. Renata, you both drew the ball so beautifully like this.
I'm sure you really see something in me, thank you.
By the way, what clubs do you use, Reina?
I use a club like this... for beginners...
Mm-hmm.
It's a beginner's club.
I'm the one who hasn't written anything on it since I bought it.
I'm a beginner, too, and this pink one is cute, and it's got sparkles, so I chose it.
So I chose this beginner's set. So I haven't really picked out the right one yet, so there are a lot of different kinds.I've chosen this one for now, a beginner's set, so I haven't really chosen the right one yet, so there's a lot of things to choose from.
I've got a lot of things to choose from, like golf clubs, and a cute little room.
So, I've got a lot of things funded, and they're all black and soft, which is really cool.
I'm going to make the LEGO reign ainda contra os dann
Mr. Roskar is a supporter of Mr. Roskie, who is currently high on the street.
I'm still working on this project, but I'm still utilizing the animation star as it is.
Yes, it's cute.
And the chou chou...
I put it on. I thought it would lift my spirits.
It was cute.
It was fun.
I'll do my best again.
I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
Bye bye!
by H.